Andrew Giovanni Winoto

UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT

Tangerang | andrewgiovanniw@gmail.com | 08119200850

About Me

I'm an undergraduate Information System BINUS University Undergraduate student who is experienced in multiple programming languages such as PHP, Java, React, Swift, MySQL, etc. I am dedicated to leveraging my skills and knowledge to contribute to the field of product management & software development.

Job Experience

Laboratory Teaching Assistant – Part Time

Feb 2022 - July 2022

- Excel in programming languages from teaching multiple programming classes.
- Delivering programming courses to BINUS University students.

Laboratory Teaching Assistant - Full Time

September 2022 – Feb 2024

• Completed game creation, web development, mobile application development, and desktop application developments projects.

Gopay Student Ambassador – Part Time

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Create marketing content to promote Gopay Application

Organization Experience

BINUS HIMSISFO Activist

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

- Organizing and managing events for BINUS University Information System students.
- Selected as Vice Coordinator of SELCAVIS 2022

Volunteer Experience

Teach For Indonesia & KMBD – DVSOS Campaign Volunteer

Mar 2022 - Mar 2022

• Creating educational videos for people with autism to help them read, write, and count.

Teach For Indonesia Volunteer Social Media Campaign Aku untuk Hijau Bumiku

2021

• Creating a social media campaign to raise community awareness of green earth.

Teach For Indonesia Volunteer Sosialisasi Anti-Rasisme Kepada Anak Panti Asuhan

2021

Planning and organizing visits to orphanages to support and provide their basic daily needs.

Education

Bina Nusantara University

2021 - Present

Information System Undergraduate - CGPA 3.84

SMAK Penabur Gading Serpong

2018 - 2021

• Science Study

Skills & abilities

- Swift
- PHP
- HTML, CSS, JS
- Java
- ReactJS, NextronJS
- C, C++, C#
- Python
- MySqL, SQLServer